You're positive it's this way?
Yeah, we're almost there!
There he is.
Mr. Kanamori!
He slashed it in the blink of an eye!
Thank you, Lord Tokito! I'm in your debt!
Mr. Kanamori!
Kotetsu, is that you?
Thank goodness you're safe!
But if I'm being honest, I thought you'd be dead by now!
Don't worry, I did too!
So you're Kanamori, is that right?
Oh?
Mr. Tokito, meet Mr. Kanamori!
If you're a swordsmith, give me a sword.
I need it now.
Oh my! Your blade is badly chipped!
Yes, that's why I came to the village.
This needs to be replaced.
Luckily, I have a sword for you. I'll go fetch it right away.
You certainly don't waste time, do you?
Well, that's a relief! And something to be thankful for!
Tanjiro asked I take care of your sword.
He said it was very important.
Oh, and that I should be understanding towards you.
Tanjiro did?
He really said that?
Indeed he did.
And so I went ahead and checked up on the first swordsmith who said to-
Mr. Kanamori! Mr. Kanamori!
We've got to head to Mr. Hagenes, because if those demons attack him-
Oh, that's right!
Come, I'll show you the way to our work shed.
This way!
I'll show you the way to our work shed.
Come, I'll show you what zurの!!
I'll show you why you might be doing this special kifiyo performance tada challenge.
It's really hard to hear.
It's gonna be me, it's gonna be my way to our work dedicated kifiyo some other works.
Like, dreams are divine also like they use разенд.
Come, I'll show you what because it doesn't work.
WeANNA do all the time.
We are вечers living well in just a bomb like Manees.
behave in as we just porting us with a rewrite and mix.
Imagine that how they will be the orcube your father.
And watch them with code.
You always do t Spinamiest.
Come on in just a long way we find this new zeitgear shoe我覺得.
Cause someone who trapped him with ice cream is one of those two cameras.
Thank you.
You can rush to the chief, as I'm sure he needs your help.
No, I can't.
Huh? Why not?
You're so annoying.
It's here.
I'm impressed that you were able to notice me.
But then again, I would expect nothing less of a Hashira.
I wonder why this rundown shed is so important to you.
Could it be you're hiding something in there you don't want me to find?
Enemy attack!
Demons! Enemy attack!
Protect the Leo from each plan!
Take out the Hashira's swords at once!
Help the chief escape!
Tensogoro!
Watch out!
These monsters have claws that are as sharp as our blades!
Retreat!
And take cover inside the building!
Never mind!
Just run!
Whoa!
A Hashira showed up!
Sorry I'm late, everyone!
Hang tight while I take care of it!
Amazing!
So fast!
So strong!
It's easy to forget because she's so cute.
But she's a Hashira.
And she's strong.
The chief!
Please go and save the chief!
Chief!
All the Demon Slayer guards who were stationed here to protect the Chief have easily been killed off!
You have my word!
As the most highly skilled person in the village, I'm not about to let you die, Chief!
But it's so big!
And abnormally quick!
My attacks have no effect on it!
I'm useless against this thing!
Please try your best not to move!
You likely have internal injuries without knowing it!
Lady Konroji?
What kind of sword is that?
Did... did the Lord Tejin forge it?
I've heard the rumors, but I can't believe it actually looks like that!
This shouldn't take long!
Blood breathing firstborn!
Shivers... of first love!
My heart... would never flutter for those who hurt others!
That's unforgivable!
Lord Tejin!
Are you alright? Hang in there!
Stay with me!
Lord Tejin, can you hear me?
Am I alright, you ask?
I'm in the arms of a beautiful girl!
I'd say I'm on cloud nine!
Oh my!
Lord Tejin, you are far too kind!
Oh no!
I think I fell on my head too!
What?
I guess you have to hold my hand now!
Oh dear, forgive me!
Is everything alright?
You back off!
What a relief!
What?
What is this?
This scent?
Stop trying to flee!
Like a pesty gnat!
What?
What is this?
This scent?
Stop trying to flee!
Like a pesty gnat!
That's right!
I got knocked out earlier by that demon with the fan!
And Nezuko came to before I did!
If Cursus, could he be any slower?
Kaurakuu, bless his entire place down!
I!
What?
That's right!
I got knocked out earlier by that demon with the fan!
And Nezuko came to before I did!
I was going to blast this place down anyway!
Think! You've got to think!
I need to inflict massive damage on the enemy with an attack they can't recover from right away!
Hey, you brat! Take this!
It's all over for you now!
Not to brag, but I'd say I outdid myself here! Now there's nowhere left for you pests to run away and hide!
Damn it! The rubble!
Nezuko, it's alright! I'm not leaving you! I need you to let go of my sword so I can get you free! Nezuko, stop! You'll cut your fingers!
That last gust of wind certainly did the trick!
Now we just have to wait for the smoke to clear up so we can finish him off!
Nezuko, please! Let go!
It's a pleasure to meet you! My name is Gyoko and I have a small request! Before I kill you, might I have a minute of your time!
Why are you holding on to me?
Because you're the one holding the sword!
If you three would be kind enough to let me, I'd be delighted to show you my beautiful artwork!
Artwork? What in the world are you talking about?
Oh, I'm so happy you ask!
Behold! I call it Death Throes of the Smiths!
Isn't it magnificent?
Feast your eyes on the centerpiece!
The hallmark of a swordsmith! Their thick, blister-ridden, soiled hands!
I pushed them to the forefront of the piece! Isn't it perfect?
Lord Kongoji! Mr. Tetsuo! Mr. Hakiike! Kotaro!
Uncle Tetsuhiro!
Yes! You're absolutely correct!
For this piece, I splurged and combined five swordsmiths to obtain the extravagant creation before you!
Still, I never expected you to be this moved by it!
Moreover, by piercing them with swords, I've truly brought out their swordsmith qualities!
And I'm sure you've noticed I left their Hyotoko masks on to juxtapose emptiness and absurdity!
Needless to say, this was a deliberate choice by yours truly!
But that's not even the best part!
Twist the sword and the art really starts to sneak!
No!
Jumping!
So, what do you think? Isn't it just marvelous?
I've perfectly captured their Death Throes!
Hey!
You better knock it off, you piece of shit!
I wasn't finished describing my artwork!
I ask that you hear me out to the end!
It can teleport from one vase to another. I see.
What I especially take pride in is the vases!
There's barely any resistance.
It got away again. It can move fast.
So now it's over there. Those vases just pop up.
You have some nerves splashing my heart!
It got away again. It can move fast.
So now it's over there. Those vases just pop up.
You have some nerves slashing my art, my magnificent creation.
Only a philistine with no eye for beauty would do such a thing.
How are those vases appearing like that?
You bastards with muscles where your brain should be can't appreciate art.
Not when you lack the critical skills my artwork demands. It's unforgivable!
Since this one seems to be intent on feeling, as opposed to that clone demon from earlier,
beheading it should be enough to kill it.
Thousand Needle Fish Kill!
Mr. Tokido!
Potenshu!
Lord Tokido!
You're getting in the way. Go hide.
I'm sorry. I... I...
Look at you, riddled with needles. A comical sight indeed.
So, how do you like it?
I'm sure the poison must be slowly numbing your limbs by now, no?
Oh, it's all so very comical.
To think you saved some worthless lives just to end up dying in a place like this.
So worthless, it doesn't matter whether they exist or not.
After all, your lives are worthless.
Who's that?
I can't remember.
Someone said the same thing to me years ago.
But who was it?
It was summer.
It was hot.
We'd left the door open.
Probably because of the heat.
The cicadas were buzzing really loud that day.
Ha ha!
Even though you certainly don't look the part,
you are still a Hashira.
I'm getting giddy thinking of all the artwork I could make from you!
That's enough.
The only thing worthless here are your words.
Blood demon art!
What a prison pot!
Death by suffocation is rather stylish.
Beautiful, isn't it?
And that spine-tingling feeling of a blade pressed up against your neck.
Now that's simply sublime.
It's no good.
I can't slash it.
Not only have I trapped you inside of there,
but your breathing techniques as well.
I can't contain myself imagining your face twisting in agony as you drown!
Ha ha ha!
Obliterating this village will be a devastating blow to you demon slayers.
And once we've brought the demon slayers to their knees,
even Ubuyashki's head will be within reach!
Yoo-hoo!
Nezuko, please let go of my sword!
Nezuko!
She's set it ablaze, using her blood!
The sword's changing color!
The temperature's rising, causing my black sword to turn red!
Shrouded in exploding blood!
This is...
Exploding blood sword!
So it turns red, right?
Mr. Samurai, your sword turns red only during the heat of battle, isn't that right?
What is this?
But why is that?
How mysterious!
When normally it's pitch black, almost like obsidian!
Who is that?
It's so beautiful, though, isn't it?
Who are you?
Wait, that's right.
This is an inherited memory.
The samurai she's talking about, could it be the swordsman with the earrings I saw?
Does that mean his sword was pitch black, too?
Then mine's just like his.
And like his, my own sword just turned red!
It changed color!
Thanks to the power of Nezuko's blood, I have this red blade.
And so, even though it was through a different method, my sword is no different than that swordsman's!
You may think you've gotten stronger, but there are always stronger demons.
I'm only flesh and blood, with a body that's scarred and battered.
And each time I've been on the brink of death, I was saved by someone.
I have to repay what they've done for me!
Everyone who's helped me come as far as I have, has but one wish, one desire!
To defeat the demons!
To protect human lives!
I have to come through for them no matter what!
You're gonna need more than cheap tricks if you want to beat me!
You can slash me all you want, but I'm not gonna feel a thing!
A burning blade, raging sword!
Lord Muzan's memories!
That's the same sword that drove Lord Muzan into a corner!
And nearly beheaded him!
I see that swordsman in him!
Hinokami Kagura!
Son of Halo Dragon!
Kid Dance!
All this time I've been thinking about that one blow.
And the reason that it decapitated Kyutaro back in the entertainment district.
How I felt in that moment, my breathing, the way I exerted myself, the way my body felt
like it was on fire, and my forehead.
Now I know.
I can do it now.
Just one more.
I need to slash all four at once.
Where's the last one?
Kenya, you're okay.
He beheaded the fourth demon.
That's great.
But hold on.
Was it simultaneous?
Kenya!
Is that Kenya?
Why does he look like that?
It's like...
No one.
to live on
are
Oh
Thank you.
Ms. Konroji, how do you go about sheathing that sword?
Oh, uh...
Poison potato!
Oh, come on, I'm just kidding, you guys!
Wow, amazing!
Really? You think it was that amazing?
But of course it is! That's Ms. Konroji for ya!
If you liked it that much, then I guess I can show it to you one more time!
Amazing, Ms. Konroji!
You think so?
Then I guess I have to show you one more time, don't I?
But this one's just for you, Tanjiro!
Wait, first things first!
Next, episode six!
Aren't you going to become a Hashiru?
There! There! There!
Amazing, amazing!